Guide to the Adler & Neilson Iron Work Company Architectural Drawings 1920-1995 PR 415
New-York Historical Society
- Files designated with a "Z", 1977-1982 (Offsite-box 35)
  U.S. P.H.S. Hospital, Staten Island, NY, 1980; Misericordia Hospital, 233rd St., Bronx, NY, 1979 (3 folders); Nassau Hospital, 1982; New York Public Library, 42nd St., NYC, 1981; New Rochelle Library, NY, 1979; Irving Trust, Wall St., NYC, 1979; Allegheny Airlines, LaGuardia Airport, NY 1978; Eastern Airlines, LaGuardia Airport, NY, 1978; Prudential Insurance Co., Haggerty, NJ, 1975; Albany Savings Bank, 1975; Columbus Hospital, 19th St., NYC, 1975; Rockefeller Center, Building 8, NYC, 1978; United Nations, 1976; American Airlines, J.F.K., 1977; Smith and Wollensky, 1980; Pratt, Brooklyn, 1982; Aqueduct Racetrack, 1980 (2 folders)
- Files designated with a "AA" (Box 1 of 2), 1977-1986 (Offsite-box 1)
  Fordham University, 1986 (2 folders); Draddy Manhattan College, 1977; Greenwich Hospital, CT, 1980; Providence Rest Home, 1980; LaGuardia Airport, 1979; Watchtower Office Building, 1980; Aqueduct Towers, 1977; Belmont Towers, 1977; Port Authority Bus Terminal 1979 (3 folders)
- Files designated with a "AA" (Box 2 of 2), 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 50)
  Columbia University: Life Science Building, Livingston and Hartley Hall, 1980-1981 (2 folders); Westbury Hotel, 69th St., NYC, 1982; Port Authority Bus Terminal, NYC, 1979; Roosevelt Hospital, 59th St., NYC, 1981
- Files designated with a "BB", 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 43)
  Xerox Center, Hartford, CT, 1987 (4 folders); Arab American Bank, 52nd St., NYC, 1986; Lane Bryant, Fifth Ave., NYC, 1986; Broad Financial Center, Whitehall St., NYC, 1985; Harmony Hall, Columbia University, 1987 (2 folders)
- Files designated with a "CC" (Box 1 of 2), 1981-1989 (Offsite-box 31)
  John Jay College, 1988 (5 folders); 575 Lexington Ave., 1989 (housed in John Jay folder); Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), 1981-1985 (4 folders)
- Files designated with a "CC" (Box 2 of 2), 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 56)
  Entire box includes drawings for the Museum of Modern Art (MOMA), New York.
- Files designated with a "DD" (Box 1 or 2), 1957-1959 (Offsite-box 21)
  International Design Center (IDC) Pedestrian Bridge, Long Island City, 1987; IDC Center, 30-30 Thomson Ave., Long Island City, NY, 1986 (7 folders)
- Files designated with a "DD" (Box 2 of 2), 1985-1991 (Offsite-box 22)
  International Design Center (IDC)I.D.C. Center, Thomson Ave., Long Island City, NY, 1985; Kiddie City, Bay Plaza, Baychester, NY, 1989; Cabrini Medical Center, East 19th St., NYC, 1988; Manhattan Savings Bank, Madison Ave., NYC, 1986; F.G.I.C. (Financial Guaranty Insurance Company) Corporation, Water St., NYC, 1986; Kenyon and Eckhardt, West 23rd St., 1986; 505 Park Ave., NYC, 1985; 740 Madison Ave., NYC, 1984; Second Avenue Theater, at 12th St., NYC, 1991 (5 folders)
- Files designated with a "EE" (Box 1 of 2), 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 2)
  Rainbow Room, 1987; Metromedia, 1982; 175 Water Street, 1985 (3 folders); Mobil Oil Corp., NYC, 1984; Brooklyn Hospital, 1981 (2 folders); Bank Leumi, 1986; Drake Hotel, NYC, 1985; Republic National Bank, NYC, 1985
- Files designated with a "EE" (Box 2 of 2), 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 40)
  Franklin General Hospital, Valley Stream, NY, 1988; LLadro Building, 57th St., NYC, 1988 (2 folders); Bromley, Fifth Ave., NYC, 1986; Lord and Taylor, Fifth Ave., NYC, 1988; Hewitt School, 75th St., NYC, 1986; Bide-a-Wee, 38th St., NYC, 1987; Chase Manhattan Bank, Pine St., 1988; 120 Fifth Ave., NYC, 1988
- Files designated with a "FF" (Box 1 of 2), 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 28)
  Jamaica Hospital, Queens, NY, 1987 (2 folders); Buckley School, 73rd St., NYC, 1988 (2 folders); Polo (store), 72nd St., NYC, 1985 (2 folders); Dobbs Ferry Chart House, Dobbs Ferry, NY, 1985; Shane O'Neil, 72nd St., NYC, 1984; C.B.S. Studios, 53rd St., NYC, 1984
- Files designated with a "FF" (Box 2 of 2), 1985-1990 (Offsite-box 46)
  "Residential Development," 150 East 85th St., NYC, 1985-1986 Federal Reserve Bank, NYC, 1990 (4 folders); Apple Bank, Westchester Sq., Bronx, NY, 1990; 200 Park Ave., NYC, 1990; Merrill Lynch, Church St., NYC, 1991; World Trade Center, Tower 1, 55th Floor, NYC, 1990; Chase Manhattan Bank, Broadway, 1989; 90 Park Ave., NYC, 1985
- Files designated with a "GG" (Box 1 of 2), 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 15)
  United Nations Development Corporation, East 44th St., 1982 (3 folders); Schermerhorn Row Block, 91 South St., NYC, 1982 (3 folders); Booth Memorial Hospital, Flushing, NY, 1983; Commerz Bank, Broad St., NYC, 1983; Tower Records, Broadway at West 66th St., NYC, 1984
- Files designated with a "GG" (Box 2 of 2), 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 38)
  Aletti, Harrison, NY, 1986; South Street Seaport Museum, NYC, 1986; The Bank of New York, Madison Ave., NYC, 1986; 461 Fifth Ave., NYC, 1987 (3 folders)
- Files designated with a "HH", 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 57)
  Cite Restaurant (1989); St. John's Hospital, Smithtown, NY (1990); St. Francis Hospital (1989); and Brooklyn Army Terminal, 4 folders (1989).
- Files designated with a "II", 1980-1989 (Offsite-box 48)
  Federated Department Stores, 1440 Broadway, NYC, 1984; "Miscellaneous" (all circa 1980s): Murphy Residence; New York Stock Exchange; Brookstone, Fulton St., NYC; Equitable Group, 195 Broadway, NYC; Xavier High School, 16th St., NYC; Pan Am Building; Smith and Wollensky; General Electric, Lexington Ave., NYC; Walt Disney Productions, Park Ave., NYC; Leo Reichenbach, 101st St., Howard Beach, NY; Traina Residence, Sag Harbor, NY; Vista International Hotel; 757 Third Ave., NYC; Colonial Church of Bayside; Gurdjieff Foundation, 63rd St., NYC; Mirette Clothing Store, Fulton St., NYC; Sheerhan Clothing Store, Fulton St., NYC; CaptainHooks; Chase Manhattan Bank, Pine St., NYC; St. Lukes Hospital, 114th St., NYC; N.Y.R.A., (New York Racing Association) Belmont, NY; Geico; Brooklyn Army Terminal; 575 Lexington Ave., NYC
- Files designated with a "JJ", 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 49)
  Lenox Hill Hospital, NYC, 1992; LaGuardia College, Long Island City, NY, 1990 (6 folders)
- Files designated with a "KK", 1989-1993 (Offsite-box 25)
  Museum of Broadcasting, West 52nd St., 1989 (3 folders); Henry Street Settlement, 1992; Ritz Tower Hotel, 57th St., 1992 (2 folders); Riverbank State Park, Riverside Drive, NYC, 1993
- Files designated with a "LL", 1988-1991 (Offsite-box 27)
  Queens College, 1988 (4 folders); Heller Residence, 89th St., NYC, 1991; Corning, Inc., Fifth Ave., NYC, 1991; Guggenheim Museum, Fifth Ave., NYC, 1991
- Files designated with a "MM", 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 18)
  LaGuardia Airport, 1992; Regent Hotel/Four Seasons Hotel, 1991 (2 folders; NOTE: contents of these folders are LaGuardia Airport Central Terminal Building); Regent Hotel, "Folder Three-Eight," East 57th St., 1991-1993 (6 folders)
- Files designated with a "NN", 1980-1990 (Offsite-box 32)
  Brooklyn Museum, 1990 (7 folders); John Jay College, 1991; Brooklyn Army Terminal, 1991; AT and T (ATT) 32 Avenue of the Americas (Sixth Ave.), 1992; "Miscellaneous" (all circa 1980s): Shearson Lehman, Greenwich St., Davidoff of Geneva, Madison Ave., NYC; New York Stock Exchange; Conde Nast, Madison Ave.; Emigrant Savings Bank, Broadway, NYC; Smith and Wollensky, 49th St., NYC; Hotel Markwell, 49th St., NYC; Westbury Hotel, 69th St., NYC; Lenox Hill Hospital, 84th St., NYC; International Design Center (IDC), Long Island City, NY; Kress Foundation, 80th St., NYC; Chase Manhattan, Pine St., Fordham University; Seidman and Seidman, Columbus Circle; Merrill Lynch, Fifth Ave.; East New York Savings Bank; Federated Department Store, Broadway, NYC; Federal Reserve Bank; Barnes and Noble; Teamsters Local 807; Dime Savings Bank, Ocean Ave., Brooklyn, NY; Cabrini Medical Center, 19th St., NYC; Doral Park Avenue Hotel; Second Avenue Theater at 12th St., NYC
- Files designated with a "OO", 1993 (Offsite-box 36)
  Ridgewood Savings Bank, Forest Hills, NY, 1993; Warner Brothers Studio Store, 57th St., NYC, 1993 (6 folders)
- Files designated with a "PP", 1993-1994 (Offsite-box 3)
  Kirkpatrick and Lockhart, NYC, 1994; Brookstone at Rockefeller Plaza, 1994; Masonic Hall, NYC, 1993; Pepsico, Purchase NY, 1993; Baruch College, East 25th St., 1993; Foley Square, NYC, 1993 (3 folders); Lenox Hill Hospital, 1994; Warner Brothers Studio Store, East 57th St., 1994; 96th Street Apartments, 1993